Benson John Lossing Collection
Benson John Lossing Collection,
- Selected index to correspondence
  1885 Jan. 23
  1886 Aug. 19
  1887 Oct. 07
  1887 Dec. 24
  1888 June 20 (2)
  1890 Apr. 19
  1890 May 12
  1890 Sep. 13
  1890 Oct. 14
  1891 Mar. 09
  Luce, Stephen Bleecker
  Ludlow, R. Fulton
  1888 June 18
  Lyon, I. S.
  McAllister, John A.
  1855 May 09
  1863 June 15
  1864 Jan. 14
  1864 Jan. 25
  1864 Mar. 25
  McClelland, R.
  1857 Feb. 04
  McComb, G. T.
  McCulloch, Robert
  1875 Dec. 21
  McDonald, John
  1852 July 12
  Mahan, Dennis Hart
  1861 Mar. 04 (misc.)
  1865 Aug. 08
  1865 Aug. 22
  1865 Aug. 29
  Marsh, L. R.
  1854 Dec. 22
  Marshall, Elizabeth C.
  Marshall, Orasmus Holmes
  1874 Apr. 14
  Martin, H. D.
  1850 Nov. 13
  Marvin, W. T. R.
  1874 Nov. 12
  Mason, D.
  1880 June 28
  Mason, E. Williams
  1868 June 19
  Mason, J.
  1861 Jan. 28
  Mason Brothers
  1857 Jan. 06
  1857 Feb. 11
  1857 Feb. 13
  1857 Feb. 21
  1858 Oct. 26
  1858 Dec. 27
  1862 Oct. 17
  1862 Oct. 20
  1863 Aug. 10
  1864 Jan. 19
  1864 Aug. 13
  1865 Apr. 11
  1865 May 05
  1865 May 10
  1865 May 16
  1865 May 17
  1865 Sep. 14
  1865 Dec. 15
  1867 Apr. 29
  1868 May. 11
  1869 Feb. 12
  1869 Aug. 25
  1881 Oct. 31
  Matthews, James
  1860 June 19
  Mayer, Brantz
  1861 Mar. 04
  1864 Oct. 02
  1869 Apr. 28
  1870 Jan. 21
  Meigs, Montgomery Cunningham
  Meline, James Florant
  1871 Nov. 30
  1872 Feb. 05
  Merritt, J. P.
  1860 Apr. 02
  Miles, Pliny
  1854 Dec. 09
  Mix, R. E.
  1852 Mar. 11
  Moore, George Henry
  1858 Jan. 22
  1861 Nov. 20
  1870 Sep. 26
  Moore, Jacob Bailey
  1886 May 06
  Moreau, Charles C.
  1874 May 15
  Moreau, Charles S.
  1872 Oct. 20
  Moreau, John B.
  1854 Dec. 11
  1859 Sep. 21
  1863 Dec. 12
  Morgan, Edwin Denison
  1882 Oct. 26
  Morris, George Pope
  1860 Mar. 27
  Morris, William Hopkins
  1865 May 15
  1865 July 03
  1887 Aug. 17
  Morse, Samuel F. B.
  1864 Aug. 19
  Moseley, William
  1854 Oct. 23
  Moss, John Calvin
  1884 Dec. 17
  Mott, Jordan Lawrence
  1883 May 29
  Muhlenberg, Henry Augustus
  1851 Jan. 04
  Munday, Eng. H.
  1862 Apr. 09
  Munsell, Joel
  1865 Jan. 31
  Munson, Lucas
  1849 Nov. 01
  Murray, David
  1882 Oct. 16
  Mutual Life Insurance Company
  Myer, Albert James
  1867 Jan. 14
  Myers, Theodorus Bailey
  1867 Oct. 1?
  1871 Oct. 28
  1876 Mar. 12
  Neill, Edward Duffield
  1872 Apr. 12
  1875 Apr. 20
  1875 Nov. 09
  1878 June 05
  Neilson, Charles
  1848 Aug. 18
  1848 Sep. 04
  Newell, C. S.
  1863 Dec. 15
  Nirtne, James
  1860 Dec. 06
  North, Edward
  1862 May 05
  1862 June 30
  Norton, Charles Benjamin
  1885 Mar. 11
  1885 May 12
  Oby, Maurice C.
  1855 Jan. 31 (enclosure: letter from Susan Putnam 1855 Jan. 30)
  O'Callaghan, Dr. (Edmund Balley?)
  Oldroyd, Osborn H.
  26 Oct. 1883
  Oliver, Henry Kemble
  1853 Apr. 13
  Onderdonk, Henry Jr.
  1850 Aug. 14
  1852 Jan. 08
  1855 June 04
  1868 Dec. 24
  1871 Oct. 24
  1871 Nov.
  1872 Feb. 04
  Oram, Elizabeth
  1853 Sep. 19
  1854 June 17
  1855 Dec. 03
  1860 May 14
  Orne, Caroline Frances
  1856 Mar. 07
  1856 Apr. 14
  1856 May 12
  1856 Aug. 29
  1857 Dec. 17
  Orton, William
  1859 June 19
  Osgood, Sam
  1860 July 11
  Paige, Lucius R.
  1888 Jan. 03
  Paine, Nathaniel
  1864 Oct. 2?
  1872 Oct. 22
  1874 May 06
  1875 July 09
  Palmer, A. W.
  1873 Mar. 08
  1873 Apr. 24?
  Parker, Amasa Junius Jr.
  1875 Aug. 13
  Parker, Caroline E.
  1868 Mar. 12
  Parsons, Usher
  1861 Aug. 17
  1861 Aug. 26
  1866 Dec. 30
  Peabody, Andrew Preston
  1862 Mar. 19 (misc.)
  Peale, Mary G.
  Peck, Oren H.
  1856 Apr. 22
  Perine, George Corbin
  Perkins, A. T.
  1875 Feb. 23
  Perry, William Stevens
  1874 Mar. 30
  Peterson, Childs
  1860 Feb. 23
  Phelps, Almira Hart Lincoln
  1851 July 14
  1854 Feb. 16
  Phoenix, S. Whitney
  1867 May 11
  Platt, William
  1850 July 24
  Poignand, D. R.
  Poillon, William
  1882 Jan. 16
  Polk, Leonidas
  1854 May 20
  Porter, Peter A.
  1860 Feb. 11
  Potter, Chandler Eastman
  1855 Jan. 13
  1855 Jan. 29
  Potter, John E.
  1874 Nov. 04
  Powell, A. Von Haller
  1861 Nov. 18
  Powers, C.
  1873 Mar. 13
  Pratt, George
  1852 June 22
  Preble, George Henry
  1884 Oct. 22
  Prime, Samuel Irenaeus
  1876 Dec. 29
  1882 Sep. 11
  Pugh, George Ellis
  Purcell, John Baptist
  1865 July 23
  Putnam, George Haven
  1871 Aug. 15
  Putnam, George Palmer
  1857 Mar. 17
  Ralph, Joseph
  1886 Mar. 16
  Ramsey, James Gettys McGready
  1860 Oct. 24
  Redfield, Justus Starr
  1868 Apr. 29
  1886 Mar. 12
  1887 Dec. 28
  Reed, William B.
  1862 Dec. 18
  Renwick, James
  1882 Sep. 26
  Richards, T. Addison
  1890 Oct. 25
  Richards, W. W.
  1891 Mar. 12
  Richardson, C. W.
  1851 Oct. 23
  Richardson, Charles Francis
  1882 Jan. 18
  1882 Jan. 20
  1882 Jan. 25
  1882 Apr. 04
  Riker, James
  1854 Apr. 17
  1878 Mar. 19
  1885 Jan. 10
  Risley, John E.
  1862 May 21
  Rives, John Cook
  1857 Feb. 09
  Rogers, John
  1882 Sep. 16
  1882 Sep. 21
  1882 Nov. 03
  Roundtable, Publishers
  Ruttenber, Edward Manning
  1855 Oct. 04
  1855 Oct. 18
  1855 Oct. 19
  Ryan, J. S.
  1855 June 12
  Sage, Aug. B.
  1858 July 09 (enclosure: watercolor of coins)
  Sammis, D. S. S.
  1877 Sep. 01
  Saratoga Monument Association
  1860 Apr. 16
  1860 Apr. 26
  1860 May 19
  Satterlee, Edward
  1877 Apr. 19
  1877 June 12
  Saunders, Frederick
  1857 Jan. 20
  1871 Dec. 21
  1874 Apr. 08
  Schuyler, Eliza H.
  1856 Sep. 12
  1858 May 23
  1861 Apr. 09
  1861 June 06
  1862 Dec. 03
  Schuyler, George Lee
  1857 June 08
  1859 Feb. 13
  1863 Feb. 04
  1870 Oct. 22
  1871 Sep. 09
  1872 Aug. 26
  1873 Jan. 05
  1873 May 06
  1875 Jan. 30
  1877 Dec. 06
  1890 Apr. 09
  1890 Apr. 16
  Schuyler, John
  1860 Apr. 17
  Schuyler, Ph?
  1865 Oct. 30
  Scott, George R.
  Sears, Clinton B.
  1881 Aug. 07
  Sedgwick, C. F.
  1850 Nov. 07
  1850 Nov. 25
  Seymour, Horatio
  1853 Jan. 12
  Seymour, John
  1871 July 27
  Shea, John Dawson Gilmary
  1882 Aug.
  Sherman, John
  1861 July 18 (misc.)
  Shubrick, William Branford
  Simms, Jeptha Root
  1872 Jan. 15
  1872 June 27
  Slocum, Joseph
  1850 May 23
  Smillie, James
  1883 Jan. 01
  1883 Jan. 08
  1883 Mar. 23
  1883 May 07
  Smith, A. B.
  Smith, Elizabeth Oakes
  1851 Mar. 01
  Smith, Joub
  1854 June 24
  Smith, Morgan L.
  1874 Sep. 03
  1874 Sep. 14
  Smith, Philip H.
  1903 Dec. 28
  Smith, T. G.
  1853 Dec. 20
  Smyth, Thomas
  1858 June 17
  Sommerville, R. A.
  1857 Apr. 18
  Southwick, Francis
  1862 Sep. 24
  1863 Nov. 11
  Sparks, Jared
  1857 Feb. 20
  Spencer, Jesse Ames
  1863 Feb. 17
  Sprague, William Buell
  Staples, Samuel Elias
  1878 Aug. 23
  Stetson, Arthur F.
  1873 Nov. 08
  Stevens, John Austin Jr.
  1863 June 26
  1863 Sep. 11
  1896 Oct. 02
  Stiles, Henry R.
  1888 Dec. 07
  Stillwell, E. G.
  Stone, William Leete
  [1861] Nov. 26
  1865 Dec. 28
  1873 July 28
  1875 Feb. 02
  1879 Apr. 17
  1879 May ?
  Strickland, E. F.
  Stryker, William Scudder
  1881 Dec. 05
  Suffern Edward S.
  10 Dec. 1864
  Sugden, Thomas D.
  1872 Nov. 25
  Swain, David Lowry
  1852 Mar. 01
  Swan, Caleb
  1867 May 22
  Swasey, Charles S.
  1864 Mar. 15
  Talbott, E. H.
  Tefft, Benjamin Franklin
  1855 Dec. 07
  Terry, Alfred Howe
  1885 Apr. 23
  Thornton, John Wingate
  1850 Nov. 01
  1852 Feb. 02
  1853 Oct. 18
  1871 Oct. 09
  1871 Nov. 20
  Thrall, George E.
  Tomlinson, A.
  1855 Dec. 31
  Townsend, Aurelia W.
  1864 Nov. 09
  Turrill, M. Sherman
  1852 May 23
  1852 June 14
  Tuttle, Charles Wesley
  1872 May 18
  Tyler, Moses Coit
  1872 Aug. 02
  1872 Nov. 13
  Van Benshoten, James Cooke
  1869 Mar. 16
  Van Ingen, Henry
  1873 Sep. 06
  Van Rensselaer, Adeline
  1855 Dec. 28
  1856 Jan. 07
  1856 Feb. ?
  1857 Dec. 03
  Van Schaack, Henry Cruger
  Vanx, George
  1872 Apr. 24
  Vincent, Frank Jr.
  1889 Mar. 02
  1890 Feb. 15
  1890 Feb. 22
  Vinton, C. Harrod
  1873 Dec. 29
  Vinton, Francis
  1859 Dec. 20
  1860 Dec. 20
  Voelckers, Theo.
  1856 Feb. 01
  Vose, Reuben
  1862 June 23
  Walker, Joseph B.
  1855 Jan. 10
  Ward, Aaron
  1867 Feb. 12
  Ward, Elijah
  1860 Jan. 16
  Ward, Richard R. (See Dean, Nicholas)
  Watson, Charles M.
  1860 Jan. 09
  Watson, John Fanning
  1853 Feb. 24
  Watson, Winslow C.
  1871 Dec. 12
  1873 Jan. 07
  n.d. (4)
  Webb, James Watson
  1883 Feb. 17
  Weir, Robert Walter
  1863 Oct. 19
  Wells, Jacob
  1870 June 24
  Wells, William V.
  1857 Sep. 16
  West, George R.
  1857 July 12
  Wetmore, Prosper Montgomery
  1851 June 24
  1860 Dec. 10
  1864 June 29
  Wheeler, John Hill
  Whitehead, William Adee
  1872 Dec. 29
  1876 Mar. 17
  Whittemore, Henry
  1878 Aug. 06
  Whittlesey, Elisha
  1862 Sep. 03
  Wilcox, H. K. W.
  1884 Oct 24
  1884 Nov. 20
  Williams, C. H. S.
  1872 Apr. 06
  Williams, J.
  1861 Nov. 14
  Williams, John Fletcher
  1871 Oct. 26
  W. S. Williams and Company
  Williams, W. W.
  1886 May 17
  Wilmarth, Lemuel Everett
  1882 Jan. 07
  Wilson, Archibald
  1874 Sep. 22
  Wilson, James Grant
  1857 Feb. 06
  1860 Oct. 22
  Wilson, James Ormond
  1865 Dec. 27
  Wilson, Joseph T.
  1888 Aug. 04
  Winsor, Justin
  1887 Mar. 04
  1887 June 23
  Winthrop, B.
  1854 Apr. 05
  Woodhull, Anna M.
  1878 May 27
  Wool, John Ellis
  1861 Jan. 20
  1861 June ?
  1861 July 15
  1867 July 04
  Wollett, Charles
  1852 Sep. 06
  Woolworth, S. B.
  1874 Mar. 11
  Wright, William
  1885 Jan. 01
  Young, Edward
  1875 Aug. 09
  Younglove, Joseph I.
  1866 June 02
  The Youth's Companion
  1890 July 15
  Zabriskie, Andrew Christian
  1874 Aug. 14
  1874 Sep. 05
  1882 June 09